[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Judd Apatows wife, who also stars in many of his movies?", "correct_answer": "Leslie Mann", "incorrect_answers": ["Katherine Heigl", "Kate Bosworth", "Kristen Wiig"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the Richland Giants head coach in the film Facing the Giants?", "correct_answer": "Bobby Lee Duke", "incorrect_answers": ["Martin Lacross", "William Horn", "Victor Blasco"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Spin City star appeared in Rick Rosenthals movie Bad Boys?", "correct_answer": "Alan Ruck", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael J. Fox", "Michael Boatman", "Charlie Sheen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the opening scene of the movie Red Dawn, the high school history teacher was giving what lesson?", "correct_answer": "on the Mongols", "incorrect_answers": ["on the Persians", "on the Greeks", "on the Huns"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following characters from the movie Aladdin was voiced by Robin Williams?", "correct_answer": "Genie", "incorrect_answers": ["Abu", "Jafar", "The sultan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Acid rain is defined as rain with a pH of below this.", "correct_answer": "5.6", "incorrect_answers": ["8.6", "2.6", "11.6"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What year was Coca-Cola developed?", "correct_answer": "1886", "incorrect_answers": ["1920", "1870", "1790"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the trick-taking game of Hearts, what have you done, if you have just shot the sun?", "correct_answer": "Taken every trick", "incorrect_answers": ["Avoided all of the points", "Taken all of the points", "Taken all but one point"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which part of the body contains the most gold?", "correct_answer": "toe nails", "incorrect_answers": ["eyelashes", "hair", "finger nails"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which subspecies of ostrich became extinct around 1966?", "correct_answer": "Middle Eastern Ostrich", "incorrect_answers": ["Red-necked Ostrich", "Southern Ostrich", "Somali Ostrich"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The number one girls name of 2006, Emily, means what?", "correct_answer": "Industrious", "incorrect_answers": ["Princess", "Flower", "Wealthy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these cocktails includes the following ingredients: Champagne, cognac, raspberry liqueur, lemon juice and fresh raspberries?", "correct_answer": "Rose of the Ritz", "incorrect_answers": ["Gimlet", "Marilyn Monroe", "Manhattan"]}]